literally online music machine where you
put something in it and a song comes out
so you could say I mean if people want
to do it hey I would love something to
be able to write a song about my iguana
wearing a top hat I mean like music
needs improv where I mean I like making
music like stupid songs as I'm saying
around the house and making things right
and that they don't make sense and I
made that level like that you just
crowdsource songs that are like people
singing and having fun top with the best
one you know it's a song about my
grandmother's pot roast whatever it
happens to be that you want to sing
about in which style and creating it
together I think would be really fun so
a literal music machine online alright
that is ideas seventeen